I had a lot of fun today.
You also got to take a photo with Inago Mask.  That's good.
Actually, um...
I had fun... because I was with you, Senpai.
I'm glad my first date was with you.
Uh... um...
I like you.
Due to the girl's efforts, the
merry-go-round of love really began to spin.
However, the spinning was troubling the boy.
I need to tell her properly myself.
But...
The painful Christmas of two years ago had made him afraid of falling in love.
Young man.
All it takes is a little confidence and courage!
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
（紗江）今日は
本当に楽しかったです
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
（純一）イナゴマスクと
写真も撮れてよかったね
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
あッ　いえ　あの…
先輩と一緒だったからです
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
あッ…
初めてのデート
先輩とでよかった～
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
あッ　あッ　え～っと…
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
好きだよ…
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
〈少女の頑張りで大きく動き始めた
恋のメリーゴーラウンド〉
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
〈しかし少年は　その動きに
ほんろうされていたのであった〉
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
はあ～ッ
ちゃんと僕から言わなきゃ
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
でも…
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
〈２年前のクリスマスに経験した
手痛い失恋が〉
〈少年を恋に臆病にさせていた〉
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
〈少年よ　ほんの少しでいい
勇気と自信を持つのだ！〉
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
・～
うわ～ッ　やっぱり　かわいい
They really are cute!
ここが紗江ちゃんの来たかった
お店なんだ
So this was the restaurant you wanted to go to.
Yes.
はい
〈少年は自分の存在が　この場で
浮いてるのを自覚していた〉
The boy realized that he didn't really belong here.
Nakata Sae Arc
Final Chapter
Lovers
あの…　ここの店員さんの制服も
かわいいですね
Um...
They have cute uniforms here too, don't they?
Huh?
えッ？
You're right.  They're cute.
ホントだ　かわいいね
この店の制服が見たかったの？
You wanted to see the uniforms of this restaurant?
えッ？　その…　はい
Huh?
Um... yes.
〈言葉を濁した少女だったが〉
She managed to fudge an answer.
But her real objective was something different.
〈でも　本当の目的は
違っていたのだった〉
Huh?  Isn't that Tyrolean café pretty close to the station?
《（美也）あれッ　このチロリアンカフェって
駅の近くのお店だよね？》
《（逢）そうだね》
《（美也）へえ～ッ　ここで一緒に》
You're right.
Wow...
I hear all the couples who have their special
banana parfait together stay in love forever!
《スペシャルバナナパフェを食べたカップルは
ず～っとラブラブなんだって》
《えッ？》
《へえ～ッ　そんな噂があるんだ》
Oh?
I didn't know about that.
〈少女が　この店に来たかったのは
スペシャルバナナパフェを食べて〉
She came to this restaurant because she wanted to share a special banana parfait with him.
She wanted him and her to stay in love forever.
〈この少年と末永くラブラブでいたいと
いう思いからなのであった〉
〈少女よ　本当に
この少年でいいのか？〉
Just a minute, girl.
Are you sure you want him?
どれにするか決まった？
Have you decided on what you want?
あの…
うん？
Um...
えっと…
うん？
Uh...
You want this?
これが食べたいの？
あッ　はい…
Recommended!
Special Banana Parfait
Uh... yes.
Recommended!
Special Banana Parfait
But I don't think I can finish it alone...
でも　１人で
食べきれるか心配で…
Well then, why don't we share it?
それじゃ　一緒に食べようか
本当ですか？
R-Really?!
ありがとうございます
フフッ
Thank you so much.
We're aiming for first place in the Best Couple contest,
ベストカップルコンテスト優勝を目指して
今日の目標は２人で
仲良くパフェを食べること！
so today's goal will be to finish this parfait together!
はい　教官
Yes, Instructor.
すごいね…
はい
Wow.
Yes.
じゃあ　いただきま～す
Well, let's dig in.
Okay.
いただきます
紗江ちゃん　大丈夫？
はッ　はい
Sae-chan, are you all right?
Y-Yes.
あんまりムリしない方がいいよ
You shouldn't force yourself.
Ah, no...
あッ　いいえ　残したら
お店の人に悪いですから
I'd feel bad for the owners if we leave any.
All right.
よ～し　じゃあ
２人で頑張って完食しちゃおう！
Let's work together to eat it all up!
あッ…
えッ　大丈夫なの？　あの人
What's with that guy?
なかなか減らないな
I'm barely making a dent...
先輩
うん？
Senpai?
I-I want to win the Best Couple contest.
私　ベストカップルコンテスト
優勝したいです
Yeah, me too.
うん　僕もだ
フフッ
〈そして　あっという間に時は過ぎ〉
Time passed in the blink of an eye, and it was the day of the Founder's Festival.
〈とうとう　創設祭　当日〉
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
The day of the Best Couple contest had arrived.
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
〈ベストカップルコンテストの日が
やってきた〉
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
Best Couple
Contest
Waiting
Room
こんな感じでいいですか？
（響）うん　ありがとう
Will this do?
Yeah, thanks.
（はるか）うわ～ッ
響　誰よりもハンサムね
Hibiki, you're the most handsome one around.
そう思わない？
はい　すごく似合ってます
Hey, don't you agree?
Yes, it looks really good on her.
Now even Nanasaki thinks so...
七咲まで　そんなこと言って…
いいじゃない
ホントに似合ってるんだから
What's wrong?  It really does look good on you.
褒められても嬉しくないわよ
どうして？
Your praise doesn't make me any happier.
Why not?
あ～あ　何で
響ちゃん女の子なの～　残念
Geez, why did Hibiki-chan have to be a girl?
It's such a shame.
はあ～ッ　でも　いいのかしら
But is this even okay?
こんなふざけたカップル
他にいないじゃない
There aren't any other joke couples like us around.
We're just making a memory, so it's fine.
思い出づくりなんだから
いいのいいの
Geez...
まったく　はるかには
かなわないわね…
I'm no match for you, Haruka.
（薫）ねえ　もしかして
そのピンクのがパートナー？
Hey.
Don't tell me that pink thing is your partner.
（梅原）たりめ～だ
それ以外に何があるってんだ
Of course it is.  Who else would it be?
すし屋のパートナーといえば魚だろ！
ププッ…
A sushi chef's partner has gotta be a fish!
「ププッ」て棚町
トロ子をバカにするなよ
What are you laughing at, Tanamachi?
Don't make fun of Toroko!
TL Note: Toro is high-grade fatty tuna; ko is a common ending for girl names.
トロ子って…
（恵子）薫　笑いすぎ
He just called it Toroko...
Kaoru, you're laughing too much.
だって…
見てみろ　このトロ子の弾力を！
But he...
Just look at how supple Toroko is!
今日のこいつは
ブリ江よりも魅力的だぜ
She's prettier than an amberjack today!
プッハハハ…
お前ら　ホント失礼だぞ！
You guys... you're really mean!
ハハッ
紗江ちゃんカチンコチンだね
Sae-chan sure looks nervous.
Y-Yes, I am...
うん　緊張しちゃって…
お兄ちゃんもね
まッ　まあな…
Onii-chan, you too.
I-I guess...
にししッ
でも結構　似合ってるよ
But you guys look good together.
うるさい
Shut up.
Sae-chan, didn't your mom prepare the outfits?
その２人の衣装　紗江ちゃんの
ママが作ってくれたんでしょ？
えっと…　コンテストに出るって
言ったらママがオーダーしてくれて
U-Um...
When I told Mom I was competing, she ordered them...
She ordered them?
・（美也）オーダー？　すごいね
That's amazing!
じゃあ　２人とも頑張って
美也　客席から応援してるね～
All right, you two.  Good luck!
I'll be cheering for you from the audience.
・（詞）今年のベストカップルコンテストは→
This year's Best Couple contest has more competitors than ever.
過去最高の出場者数で
それだけ激戦となっています→
The competition will be fierce!
その中で栄えある大賞に輝くのは
どのカップルなのか？
Best Couple Contest
Out of all these lovely participants,
who will win the glorious grand prize?
Best Couple Contest
早速　登場していただきましょう
Let's get them on the stage!
・（詞）では　エントリーナンバー１番
２年Ａ組→
First up, entry number one.
Umehara Masayoshi-san from class 2-A and Toroko-san!
梅原正吉さん　トロ子さん
・（観客Ａ）トロ子！
・（観客Ｂ）お似合いだぞ
Toroko!
You guys really match!
諸君　今日は俺とトロ子のために
集まってくれてありがと～ッ
Ladies and gentlemen, thanks for
coming out today for me and Toroko!
・（観客Ｃ）トロ子を幸せにね
Make Toroko happy!
トロ子　今夜は
２人で解体ショーだな
Toroko, I'm gonna open you up tonight.
おッ　解体か？
朝までコースか？
Open her up, huh?
All night long?
・（琉璃子）何だか急に　お客さんが
いなくなってしまったな
The number of customers suddenly dropped.
（愛歌）まさに閑古鳥
Just like a business slump.
That's because they're doing a
Best Couple contest in the gym.
（梨穂子）体育館でベストカップルコンテストを
やってるからですよ
It looks like everyone went over there.
みんな　そっちに
行っちゃったみたいです
I see.
（琉璃子）そっか　なら仕方ない
この間にゆっくり休憩するか
In that case, I guess we'll just have to enjoy the break.
じゃあ
お茶でも　たてますか？
Should I make some tea then?
Allow me.
私が　たてる
Wait a minute!
ちょっと待て！　この前みたいな
ロシアンルーレットお点前は　なしだ
None of that Russian Roulette stuff you pulled last time.
Do it normally this time.
普通にしろよ
残念…
アハハハッ
Pity.
Morishima-senpai!
森島せんぱ～い！
・（観客Ｄ）せんぱ～い！
Senpai!
Now, let's introduce the final couple.
では　最後のカップルを紹介します
２年Ａ組　橘純一さんと
１年Ａ組　中多紗江さんです
Tachibana Junichi-san from class 2-A and Nakata Sae-san from class 1-A!
（拍手）
紗江ちゃん？
Sae-chan?
はッ　はい…
Y-Yes...
あッ
行こう
Let's go.
僕がついてるよ
I'll be right with you.
Yes.
はい
・（詞）
何とも初々しいカップルです
What a charming couple.
This looks just like a marriage ceremony.
まるで結婚式みたいですね
何て　かわいいの…
How adorable...
いつもの中多さんと違って
大人っぽいね
Nakata-san looks different today.
Just like a grown-up.
Yeah, Sae-chan's beautiful.
うん　紗江ちゃんキレイ
あッ
大丈夫？
すみません
Are you okay?
Sorry.
では　一問一答です　お互いに
好きなところをお願いします
Now for some Q&A.
Tell us what you like about each other.
Let's start with you, Tachibana-san.  Well?
まずは橘さん　どうですか？
Um...
あの…　かわいらしいところです！
She's really cute!
（詞）では　中多さんは？
And you, Nakata-san?
たッ…
頼りになる教官なところです
H-He's a really reliable instructor!
あッ
えッ　教官？
Huh?  Instructor?
Uh, I mean...
あッ　いえ　あの…
頼りになるところです
H-He's really reliable.
I see.
なるほど
はい
Yes.
橘さん　中多さん
ありがとうございました
Tachibana-san and Nakata-san.
Thank you very much.
・（詞）さて　これで全てのカップルに
登場していただきました→
With that, we've now seen all of the couples.
それでは　審査員の先生には
審査に入っていただきます
Now the judges will begin their evaluations.
優勝は俺らがもらったが
２位は　お前らがとれよ
I know we've got first down for sure, but you guys better take second!
Right... that's some serious confidence.
はいはい　大した自信だな
ぶっちゃけ　トロ子と中多さんは
To be frank, Toroko and Nakata-san are worthy rivals,
いい勝負だが　俺とお前で
圧倒的な差がついたからな
but I'm clearly way better than you are.
なあ　トロ子
ああ　そうかい
Right, Toroko?
I see.
〈少年は　それ以上
友人に　つっこめなかった〉
The boy had nothing more to say to his friend.
Thank you for waiting!
お待たせいたしました
審査結果が出ました→
The judges' results are in.
では　発表します！→
Announcing the results!
本年度ベストカップルは
This year's best couple is...
Unanimously...
・（詞）審査員　満場一致で…
・（詞）塚原響さん
森島はるかさんに決定しました
Tsukahara Hibiki-san and Morishima Haruka-san!
Congratulations!
おめでとうございます
会場の皆様は
Let's all give them a round of applause!
お２人に
盛大な拍手をお願いします
ありがとう
Thank you!
続いて　第２位は…→
In second place we have...
橘純一さん　中多紗江さんの
カップルです
Tachibana Junichi-san and Nakata Sae-san!
It looks like everyone voted for us out of amusement.
私達はネタで
票を集めたようなものだから
本当の１位は　あのカップルね
First place really should've gone to them.
Yeah, they're really cute!
うん　ホントにかわいい
うちに連れて帰りたいくらい
I want to take them home with me.
・（響）こらこら
Hey, now.
見事１位に輝いた塚原　森島
両先輩には山猫屋のディナー券を
The couple that shone brightest, Tsukahara-senpai and Morishima-senpai, win tickets to the Yamaneko Restaurant.
And the couple that shone second-brightest, Tachibana-san and Nakata-san...
そして　２位に輝いた
橘さんと中多さんには→
...win tickets to a private room at the movies!
映画館　個室シートチケットをプレゼントします
それぞれ　カップルでお楽しみください
Both couples, please enjoy these prizes together!
Sorry.
Huh?
We weren't able to win.
No, it's not your fault, Senpai.
It's my fault.
Huh?
I mean, you were better-looking than Tsukahara-senpai,
but we lost because I was no match for Morishima-senpai.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
That's not true!
You were cuter than Morishima-senpai, Sae-chan.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, about the movie...
ゴメンね
えッ？
Yes...
優勝できなくて
Is tomorrow okay?
A-Are you sure?
いえ　先輩のせいじゃないです
私のせいです
It's Christmas...
Huh?
Yeah.  Well?
えッ？
だって
I'd love to.
They weren't able to win the Best Couple contest, but they put up a brave fight.
She was too embarrassed to tell the truth,
so she said her mother ordered the costumes.
However, she actually sewed the pure white dress and suit herself.
And she was rewarded for her efforts.
先輩は塚原先輩より
全然カッコイイのに…
Sorry!
Did you wait long?
私が森島先輩に　かなわなかった
からダメだったんです
Not really... you're here early too.
Sae-chan, you came here early again?
ゴメンなさい　先輩
そんなことないよ
Yes.
森島先輩より紗江ちゃんの方が
かわいかったよ
You can just come at the appointed time from now on.
えッ…　ホントですか？
From now on...?
Okay!
うん
I also wanna know what it's like to wait for you, Sae-chan.
あッ　そうだ　映画なんだけど
N-No way!
はい
明日は　どうかな？
There's no way I could make you wait for me, Senpai!
Nothing wrong with it once in a while.
えッ　いいんですか？
クリスマスなのに…
I-I can't...
えッ？　うん　どう？
Sae?
It's been so long!  How are you?
もちろん大丈夫です
I'm good.
〈ベストカップルコンテストの優勝は
逃したものの〉
Hey, is he your boyfriend?
〈２人の健闘は　すばらしかった〉
Is this a Christmas date?
〈少女は本当のことを言うのが
恥ずかしくて〉
That's nice!
I want a boyfriend too.
〈母親がオーダーしたことにしていたが
実は　あの純白のドレスとスーツは〉
You're even more adorable than before you moved for some reason!
Could this be the power of love?
〈少女が自ら縫ったものだった〉
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
〈その努力が
報われた結果であった〉
Well, best of luck to you!
Huh?  For what?
This is a really nice room.
いい感じの部屋だね
はい
Yes.
おお～ッ　このイス
すごく座り心地いいよ
Whoa, this couch is really comfortable!
Sae-chan, have a seat.
紗江ちゃんも座ったら？
あッ　はい
Okay.
I-I'm going to the bathroom.
トイレに行ってくる
何か飲み物買ってきます
I-I'll go buy some drinks.
W-What the heck am I doing?
何をやってるんだよ　僕
今日はちゃんと言わなきゃ
I've got to tell her today.
ダメじゃないか
I have to.
（英語で話す）
はあッ？
うッ　ゲホッ　ゲホッ
あれッ　コート脱いだんだ
Huh?
You... took your coat off.
あッ　ここ
暖房がきいてて暑かったので
Ah, they turned up the heat in here and it got warm...
Senpai, your face is all red.
先輩　顔が真っ赤です
やっぱり少し暑いですよね
It really is quite hot in here, isn't it?
あッ　ジュース飲んでください
Have some juice.
本当に大丈夫ですか？
Are you sure you're okay?
はあ～ッ　少し落ち着いたよ
I feel a little better now.
よかった
正直いうと
That's good.
To be honest, I was quite taken by your outfit.
紗江ちゃんの服に
ちょっとドキドキしちゃった
Really?
ホントですか？
うッ　うん
Y-Yeah...
よかった　実は…
あッ
I'm glad.  Actually...
美也に聞いたんだ
美也ちゃんに聞いたんです
So you asked Miya for advice.
I asked Miya-chan for advice.
フフッ
ハハハ…
似合うかどうか　自信が
なかったんですけど　よかった
I wasn't confident if it would look okay or not, but I'm glad.
よく似合ってるよ
It looks really good on you.
Senpai, this movie...
先輩　この作品　撮影後に
Love's Course
Love's Destination...
It says that after filming, the relationship between the director and the lead actress was revealed.
監督さんと主演女優さんの交際が
発覚したんですって
恋人同士だから
監督さんが女優さんの美しさを
Love's Course
Love's Destination...
Because they were lovers, he was able to capture her beauty perfectly on screen.
最大限に引き出せたのではって
評判になっているそうです
He gained a reputation for it.
そうなんだ…
Really?
あッ！
どうかしましたか？
What's the matter?
この監督さんに
さっきトイレで会ったよ
I saw the director in the bathroom earlier!
えッ　ホントですか？　じゃあ
主演女優さんも来てるのかな？
What?
Really?
I wonder if the actress is here too.
Who knows?
どうかな？
だって　お２人は
Well, the two of them are lovers.
恋人同士なんですよね
だったら　きっと一緒に…
So I'm sure they'd come together...
そうだね
Yeah.
I can't really see.
よく分からないね
はい　そうですね
Yeah.
You're right.
あッ…
うん？
ああッ…
あッ
監督さんの
女優さんに対する思いが
The director's feelings for the actress really came out on the screen.
スクリーンに
あふれている気がします
It was full of his love for her.
愛情に満ちていますね
僕の思いだって負けてないよ
えッ？
My feelings are just as strong.
僕の方が　キレイに撮れるさ
I could capture beauty even better.
I'm the director, and Sae-chan, you're the actress I'm filming.
僕は監督だ　紗江ちゃん　君は
今から僕が撮るフィルムの主演女優だ
えッ？　はッ　恥ずかしいです
What?
I-It's embarrassing.
ダメダメ
カメラから逃げちゃダメだよ
No, no.  You shouldn't hide from the camera.
Well, get ready!
さあ　覚悟を決めて！
さあ　さあ　さあ
Well, well, well!
うわッ！
わッ！
僕は…
I...
先輩？
Senpai?
Don't be afraid of failure, young man.
〈少年よ　失敗を恐れるな
勇気さえあれば　うまくいく〉
If you have courage, things will go just fine!
先輩…
Senpai...
Really... thank you so much for everything.
ホントに　いろいろ
ありがとうございました
紗江ちゃん？
Sae-chan?
あッ　すみません
ゴメン
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
違います　悲しいんじゃなくて…
It's not that.
I'm not upset.
えッ？
Huh?
Spending time with you like this, Senpai...
先輩と　こうして過ごせて…
すごく嬉しいです
It makes me really happy.
僕も嬉しいよ
I'm happy too.
あの…　先輩　何か言ってください
Um, Senpai...
Please say something.
うッ　うん
あッ　いえ…
O-Okay.
Ah, no...
ゴメン　何か
うまく言葉にできなくて
Sorry, I can't really put it into words.
謝らないでください
先輩は悪くないです
Please don't apologize.
You've done nothing wrong.
あッ　うん…
Y-Yeah.
今日は　ちゃんと言うよ
えッ？
I'm gonna say it today.
先輩？
Senpai?
紗江ちゃんが好きだ　大好きなんだ
I like you, Sae-chan.
I really do.
先輩…
Senpai...
年上のクセに頼りないし　気のきいた
ことも言えない僕だけど
Even though I'm older, unreliable, and insensitive...
そんなことないです
私　先輩に出会ってから
That's not true at all!
Ever since I met you, Senpai...
いろいろ変われて
すごく毎日が楽しくて…
I began to change, and every day is filled with so much fun...
僕　紗江ちゃんを好きな気持ちは
誰にも負けない
My feelings of love for you won't lose to anyone else's.
紗江ちゃん…
Sae-chan...
先輩…
Senpai...
先輩　私　幸せです
あッ…
Senpai...
I'm so happy.
〈その瞬間　少年は少女の瞳に胸を
打ちぬかれキュン死したのである〉
At that moment, her eyes pierced through his heart, and he died from moe.
Moe Death
To die from moe is to have your chest tighten suddenly,
〈キュン死とは
一瞬にして胸がキュンとなり〉
〈そのまま　心を奪われて
昇天することである〉
and have your heart taken from you as you rise to paradise.
先輩？　先輩？
Senpai?  Senpai?!
せんぱ～い！
Senpai!
うわ～ッ
キレイだね
It's so pretty.
あの…
うん？
Um...
Yeah?
Do you think that we look like a couple?
私達　カップルに
見えるでしょうか？
Yeah, we do.
うん　見えるよ　だって僕達
Because we really are lovers.
ホントに恋人同士なんだから
Yes.
はい
あッ　雪
ホントだ
Ah, it's snowing.
It is.
どうりで今日は寒いと思った
雪　積もるといいですね
No wonder I thought it was cold today.
I hope the snow piles up.
〈失恋のトラウマを抱え　奥手で
臆病でチキンであった少年と〉
A shy, cowardly chicken of a boy traumatized by his first love...
〈極度に内気な少女の恋の物語は
これで終わりである〉
...and the shyest girl imaginable.
Their love story now comes to a close.
〈まだ　ようやく一歩を
踏み出したばかりの２人が〉
At long last, they've only just taken one step forward,
but let's wish their love may last forever from the bottom of our hearts.
〈この先　ずっとラブラブなままで
いられるよう心から願おう〉
〈そして　しばらくあとの
２人はというと…〉
And after some time had passed...
All right, looking good, Sae-chan.
よしッ　いいよいいよ　紗江ちゃん
あッ　はい
Ah... yes!
じゃ　次のポーズはね
にぃに
Okay, for the next pose-
Nii-nii!
Are you filming some weird movie again?
またヘンな映画撮ってるんでしょ
えッ？　美也
美也ちゃん
わ～ッ　紗江ちゃんのペンギン姿
Miya...
Miya-chan.
Sae-chan, you look so cute as a penguin!
かわいい～ッ
邪魔するなよ
Hey, don't interfere.
And what's with that outfit?
あと　その格好…　何だ？
It's a black kitty!
黒ニャンコだよ
みゃーも仲間に入れて　ニャン
Let me play too, meow!
美也ちゃんの　かわいい～
Miya-chan, you look really cute.
ニャハッ　嬉しいニャン
I'm so happy, meow~
ねえ　ほら早く
仕方ないな～
Hey, come on, hurry up!
Guess I have no choice.
美也も撮ってやるよ
やった～！
Miya, I'll film you too.
Yay!
Senpai, from now on and forever...
〈先輩　これからもず～っと〉
〈私を一番かわいく
撮ってくださいね〉
Film me the cutest I can be.
・～
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
会いたい気持ちでなぞる指くるくる
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
合えない午後なら浮かべるはフワフワ
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
Anata no koto omou dake de
あなたの事想うだけで
Just thinking about you
Watashi shiawase desu
私幸せです
Makes me so happy
Ippai oshaberi shitakute
いっぱいお喋りしたくて
I want to have long chats with you
Ima sugu ni
今すぐに
Right away
Itsumo futarikiri dattara
いつも二人きりだったら
If only we could always be alone together
Ii no ni na
いいのにな
It would be so nice
Tsugi ni au made wa sukoshi oazuke tsurai kedo
次に合うまでは少しお預け辛いけど
It'll be hard to wait until the next time we can meet
Motto daisuki ni nareru hazu ne
もっと大好きになれるはずね
But in the meantime I'll grow to love you even more
Nareru hazu ne
なれるはずね
I'll love you even more
Aitai kimochi de nazoru yubi kurukuru
会いたい気持ちでなぞる指くるくる
My twirling finger traces my feelings of missing you
Aenai gogo nara ukaberu wa fuwafuwa
会えない午後なら浮かべるはフワフワ
I think about you when I can't see you in the afternoon
My Darling itsumo soba ni itai
マイダーリン　いつも側に居たい
My darling, I want to always be by your side
Zutto anata shika mienai wa
ずっとあなたしか見えないわ
I'll never look at anyone but you
Daisuki yo
大好きよ
I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, boss!
W-What's the matter, Umehara?
What are you doing in the preview?
Don't tell me you're the heroine starting next week!
Hey now, obviously not.
Y-You're right.  Thank goodness.
According to my data, the next girl's pretty tough.
Really?
Am I gonna be all right?
Next episode: "Worst".
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai Arc: Chapter 1
Worst
H-Hey, wait a second.
Doesn't that title sound ominous?
Yeah, you'd better get ready.